Cheng Ze
You said it yourself
Business partnerships naturally
require practical considerations
So you admit it
You admit choosing Su Yurou
was for her key authorization
I didn't say that
Then what exactly did you say
Sis
I admit I like Cheng Ze
But who can control their feelings
Liking someone isn't wrong
But wearing someone else's wedding ring
standing at their wedding
and claiming you're innocent
is just not right
If she didn't really want it
why didn't she take it off earlier
Crying now won't do any good
I can give the ring back
I really don't want to make you sad
No need
The ring isn't the point
The point is why he chose you
which has already been made clear
Calmer than earlier
I wasn't calm enough just now
I wanted to tear the place apart earlier